symbaloo.com 2017-05-23

# Disclaimer

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use Symbaloo's services.

**Personal Information**

* You need a Symbaloo Account to create a Symbaloo homepage that is accessible from any Internet-connected computer. Symbaloo asks for some personal information when you create a Symbaloo Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A Symbaloo Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration.  
* You may also create a Symbaloo homepage that is accessible only from your computer, with preference settings stored in a cookie.  
* You may choose to submit additional information in order to personalize your homepage (such as your city to customize your weather forecast).  
* When you use Symbaloo, Symbaloo's servers automatically record log information which may include information about your preference settings. 

**Uses**

* Symbaloo maintains and processes personal information in order to provide your personalized homepage and other services. This information will be stored in a cookie on your machine and sent to Symbaloo when you request the page. 

**Your choices**

* You can terminate your Symbaloo Account at any time.  
* You can change or delete the preference settings in your personalized homepage at any time.  
* You can delete your cookie with your preferences stored. 

**Information Sharing**

* Some sections on Symbaloo.com are provided by third parties, who may receive and process your requests and preference settings for that section in order to provide their service. In some cases, other information including one or more of your Symbaloo cookies may also be technically available to the third party, although third parties are prohibited by contract from accessing your Symbaloo cookies or other information unrelated to the section they provide. When you add one of these sections to your page, we will let you know. Use of your information by these third parties is not governed by this Privacy Policy.  
* We may share aggregate statistics about Personalized Homepage usage with our business partners. We will not share personally identifying information with these partners or any third parties, except under the narrow circumstances described in the Symbaloo Privacy Policy. 

**More information**

If you have additional questions, please contact us any time. Or write to us at:

**Privacy Matters**  

violations[at]symbaloo.com

**Symbaloo HQ Netherlands**  
Symbaloo BV  
Burgwal 47  
2611 GG   
Delft  
Netherlands  
015-2129006 |  **Symbaloo office United States**  
K&S Marketing Impact Inc.  
2915 Redhill Ave C103  
92626  
Costa Mesa  
USA  
(949) 791-9348   
---|---
